<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PloiestiCityTour</string>
    <string name="about_ploiesti1">Ploiești is a city and county seat in Prahova County, Romania.Part of the historical region of Muntenia, it is located 56 km (35 mi) north of Bucharest. The area of the city is around 60 km2. It borders the Blejoi village in the north, Bărcănești and Brazi villages in the south, Târgșoru Vechi in the west and Bucov village in the east. Ploiești has direct access to the Prahova Valley, one of the most important alpine tourism areas in Romania.</string>
    <string name="about_ploiesti2">Ploiești is an important transport hub, linking Bucharest with Transylvania and Moldavia. According to the 2011 Romanian census, there were 201,226 people living within the city of Ploiești, making it the 9th most populous in the country. Though likely settled much earlier, Ploiești was first mentioned in documents in the 16th century, during the reign of Mihai Viteazul (Michael the Brave), Prince of Wallachia. It flourished as a center for trade and handicraft manufacturing in the 17th and 18th centuries. The road connecting Ploiești to Brașov opened in 1864, and the railway arrived in 1882. Many schools and hospitals date from this time.</string>
    <string name="about_ploiesti3">In the mid-19th century the Ploiești region was one of the world\'s leading oil extraction and refinery sites. The world\'s first large refinery[4] opened at Ploiești in 1856-1857, with US investment. The city is also remembered as the site of the self-styled Republic of Ploiești, a short-lived 1870 revolt against the Romanian monarchy.</string>
    <string name="about_ploiesti4">Ploiești\'s oil production made it a target during the invasion of Romania by the Central Powers in 1916, but a British Army operation under John Norton-Griffiths destroyed production and sabotaged much of the infrastructure of the industry.[5] Though likely settled much earlier, Ploiești was first mentioned in documents in the 16th century, during the reign of Mihai Viteazul (Michael the Brave), Prince of Wallachia. It flourished as a center for trade and handicraft manufacturing in the 17th and 18th centuries. The road connecting Ploiești to Brașov opened in 1864, and the railway arrived in 1882. Many schools and hospitals date from this time.</string>
    <string name="about_ploiesti5">In the mid-19th century the Ploiești region was one of the world\'s leading oil extraction and refinery sites. The world\'s first large refinery[4] opened at Ploiești in 1856-1857, with US investment. The city is also remembered as the site of the self-styled Republic of Ploiești, a short-lived 1870 revolt against the Romanian monarchy.</string>
    <string name="about_ploiesti6">Ploiești\'s oil production made it a target during the invasion of Romania by the Central Powers in 1916, but a British Army operation under John Norton-Griffiths destroyed production and sabotaged much of the infrastructure of the industry.</string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="attractions">Attractions Nearby</string>
    <string name="about_ploiesti">About Ploiesti</string>

</resources>
